Chandler, Alfred D., 1918-2007. Papers, 1941-2004: A Finding Aid
Alfred D. Chandler papers, 1940-2007
- Series V. Appointment Calendars, 1977-1987
  - Appointment Calendar, March-April 1978 (Box 193, f. 9)
  - Appointment Calendar, May-June 1978 (Box 193, f. 10)
  - Appointment Calendar, Sept.-Oct. 1978 (Box 193, f. 11)
  - Appointment Calendar, Nov.-Dec. 1978 (Box 193, f. 12)
  - Appointment Calendar, Jan.-Feb. 1979 (Box 193, f. 13)
  - Appointment Calendar, March-April 1979 (Box 193, f. 14)
  - Appointment Calendar, May-June 1979 (Box 193, f. 15)
  - Appointment Calendar, Sept.-Oct. 1979 (Box 193, f. 16)
  - Appointment Calendar, Nov.-Dec. 1979 (Box 193, f. 17)
  - Appointment Calendar, Jan.-Feb. 1980 (Box 193, f. 18)
  - Appointment Calendar, March-April 1980 (Box 193, f. 19)
  - Appointment Calendar, May-June 1980 (Box 193, f. 20)
  - Appointment Calendar, Sept.-Oct. 1980 (Box 193, f. 21)
  - Appointment Calendar, Nov.-Dec. 1980 (Box 193, f. 22)
  - Appointment Calendar, Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 194, f. 1)
  - Appointment Calendar, March-April 1981 (Box 194, f. 2)
  - Appointment Calendar, May-June 1981 (Box 194, f. 3)
  - Appointment Calendar, Sept.-Oct. 1981 (Box 194, f. 4)
  - Appointment Calendar, Nov.-Dec. 1981 (Box 194, f. 5)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1982 (Box 194, f. 6)
  - Appointment Calendar, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 194, f. 7)
  - Appointment Calendar, March-April 1983 (Box 194, f. 8)
  - Appointment Calendar, May-July 1983 (Box 194, f. 9)
  - Appointment Calendar, Sept.-Oct. 1983 (Box 194, f. 10)
  - Appointment Calendar, Nov.-Dec. 1983 (Box 194, f. 11)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1983 (Box 194, f. 12)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1984 (Box 194, f. 13)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1985 (Box 194, f. 14)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1986 (Box 194, f. 15)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1987 (Box 194, f. 1)
- Series VI. Audio-Visual Records, 1940-2007
  This series consists of audio-visual materials kept by Alfred Chandler and includes photographs, videos, and Dictabelt recordings. Photographs consist of personal photographs as well as photographs taken at various events. Video recordings are of Chandler being interviewed and at the Harvard commencement. The Dictabelts include recordings of Alfred Chandler dictating research notes and commentaries on student work while at MIT and Johns Hopkins University.
  - Subseries A. Photographs, circa 1940-2007
    . This subseries contains photographs of Alfred Chandler and family, his professional and academic colleagues and professional events. Many of the photographs were removed from correspondence files.
    - Personal photos, ca. 1940-2007 (Box 246, f. 4)
    - Probably a photograph of Chandler with faculty at Naval War College (where he was a consultant), 1954 (Box 246, f. 5)
    - Photographs, 1970 (Box 196, f. 5)
    - Photographs of Chandler with Robert deGast, Gettysburgh, 1970 (Box 246, f. 17)
    - "Jan. 74- 1st Fuji conference?" (Box 246, f. 6)
    - Photograph of Chandler and Yoshio Katsura, 1979 (Box 246, f. 7)
    - Group photograph from the Japan Conference, 1985 (Box 246, f. 8)
    - Photographs from small album entitled, " Al and Staff and Students," ca. 1986-1993 (Box 246, f. 9)
    - Photograph of Chandler at the Winter Quarterly Commencement Ceremony at Ohio State University, 1987 (Box 246, f. 10)
    - Photograph of Chandler with Yasura Ohya, 1990 (Box 246, f. 11)
    - Photographs from various commencement ceremonies where Chandler received honorary degrees, 1992-2002 (Box 246, f. 12)
    - Photograph of Chandler with Japanese colleagues, 1997 (Box 246, f. 13)
    - AEC HAC: Photographs (Box 196, f. 6)
    - Harvard Business School professional photograph of Chandler, undated (Box 246, f. 14)
    - Christmas Cards with photographs, 1984-1987 (Box 196, f. 7)
    - Christmas Cards with photographs, 1987-2007 (Box 246, f. 15)
  - Subseries B. Dictabelt Recordings, circa 1965
    This subseries contains Dictabelt recordings of Alfred Chandler dictating research notes and commentaries on student work while at MIT and Johns Hopkins University. Includes dictated notes related to research on DuPont, General Motors and Standard Oil. The recordings were made around 1965. Some of the transcriptions of the recordings can be found throughout the collection (primarily with MIT and Johns Hopkins University related material) as typescripts filed with research notes.
    Note that only select recordings have been transcribed.
    - Index (Box 197, f. 1)
    - Tape Nos. 1-3: General Motors and Standard Oil (GM/SO): Administration Committee: Board of Directors/By-laws, 1937 (Box 197, f. 2)
    - Tape Nos. 4-5: GM/SO: Administration Committee, 1938 (Box 197, f. 3)
    - Tape Nos. 6-9: GM/SO: Administration Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 197, f. 4)
    - Tape Nos.10-12: GM/SO: Administration Committee, 1942, 1946 (Box 197, f. 5)
    - Tape Nos. 13-16: GM/SO: Distribution Group, 1934-1935, 1940, 1946 (Box 197, f. 6)
    - Tape Nos. 17-20: GM/SO: Distribution Group, 1935, 1937 1939 (Box 197, f. 7)
    - Tape No. 21: GM/SO: Engineering Policy, 1945-1946, 1955 (Box 197, f. 8)
    - Tape Nos. 22-24: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1921 (Box 197, f. 9)
    - Tape Nos. 25-26: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1921 (Box 197, f. 10)
    - Tape Nos. 27-30: 45: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 197, f. 11)
    - Tape Nos. 31-34: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1924-1925 (Box 197, f. 12)
    - Tape Nos. 35-36: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1925 (Box 197, f. 13)
    - Tape Nos. 37-39: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1926-1931 (Box 197, f. 14)
    - Tape Nos. 40-42: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1932-1934 (Box 197, f. 15)
    - Tape Nos. 43-44: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1935-1937 (Box 197, f. 16)
    - Tape Nos. 46-49: GM/SO: Finance Committee, 1921-1937 (Box 197, f. 17)
    - Tape Nos. 50-52: GM/SO: General Letters, 1922-1924, 1937-1947 (Box 197, f. 18)
    - Tape Nos. 53-55: GM/SO: General Technical, 1923 (Box 197, f. 19)
    - Tape Nos. 56-59: GM/SO: General Sales, 1921-1933 (Box 197, f. 20)
    - Tape Nos. 60-61: GM/SO: Operations Committee, 1921 (Box 197, f. 21)
    - Tape Nos. 62-64: GM/SO: Operations Committee, 1921-1925 (Box 197, f. 22)
    - Tape Nos. 65-68: GM/SO: Operations Policy Committee, 1937-1946 (Box 197, f. 23)
    - Dictabelts: Problem File (Box 197, f. 23a)
    - Tape Nos. 69-72: GM/SO: Product Group, 1937-1944 (Box 197, f. 24)
    - Tape Nos. 73-75: GM/SO: Reports, 1924, 1930 (Box 197, f. 25)
    - Tape Nos. 76-78: GM/SO: Reports, 1930; undated (Box 197, f. 26)
    - Tape Nos. 79-80: GM/SO: Notes on Wilkerson/Correspondence and Reports (Box 197, f. 27)
    - Tape Nos. 81-83: GM/SO: Executive Committee/Correspondence and Reports/ Technical Cte (Box 197, f. 28)
    - Tape Nos. 84-86: GM/ SO: Executive Committee, 1921-1923 (Box 197, f. 29)
    - Tape Nos. 87-88: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1923 (Box 197, f. 30)
    - Tape Nos. 89-91: GM/SO: Executive Committee, 1924-1926 (Box 197, f. 31)
    - Tape Nos. 92-94: GM/SO: Executive Committee, Correspondence and Reports (Box 197, f. 32)
    - Tape Nos. 95-98: GM/SO: Executive Committee: Correspondence and Reports (Box 197, f. 33)
    - Tape Nos. 99-100b GM/SO: General Sales Cte: 1924-1927 (Box 197, f. 34)
    - Tape Nos. 101-104: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #4; #21 (Box 197, f. 35)
    - Tape Nos. 105-108: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #22; #23 (Box 197, f. 36)
    - Tape Nos. 119-112: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #23; #26 (Box 197, f. 37)
    - Tape Nos. 113-116: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #26; #29; #40 (Box 197, f. 38)
    - Tape Nos. 117-120: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #71; #107; #189 (Box 197, f. 39)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: Clark Papers, #189 (Box 197, f. 40)
    - Tape Nos. 125-128: GM/SO: Esso Circular letters (Box 197, f. 41)
    - Tape Nos. 129-132: GM/SO: Esso Circular letters (Box 197, f. 42)
    - Tape Nos. 129-132: GM/SO: Development Dept. (Box 197, f. 43)
    - Tape Nos. 129-132: GM/SO: Development Dept (Box 197, f. 44)
    - Tape Nos. 129-132: GM/SO: Manufacturing Dept (Box 197, f. 45)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: Manufacturing Dept (Box 197, f. 46)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: The Lamp (Box 197, f. 47)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: The Lamp (Box 197, f. 48)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: Outline of Standard Oil of New Jersey (SONJ) (Box 197, f. 49)
    - Tape Nos. 121-124: GM/SO: Outline of SONJ/Enterprise in Production (Box 197, f. 50)
    - Tape Nos. 1-3: General (Box 197, f. 51)
    - Tape Nos. 4-5: General (Box 197, f. 52)
    - Tape Nos. 6-8: General (Box 197, f. 53)
    - Tape Nos. 9-11: General (Box 197, f. 54)
    - Tape Nos. 12-13: General (Box 197, f. 55)
    - Tape Nos. 14-16: General (Box 197, f. 56)
    - Tape Nos. 17-19: General (Box 197, f. 57)
    - Tape Nos. 20-21: General (Box 197, f. 58)
    - Tape Nos. 22-23: General (Box 197, f. 59)
    - Tape Nos. 24-25: General (Box 197, f. 60)
    - Tape Nos. 26-28: General (Box 197, f. 61)
    - Tape Nos. 29-31: General (Box 197, f. 62)
    - Tape Nos. 32-33: General (Box 197, f. 63)
    - Tape Nos. 34-36: General (Box 197, f. 64)
    - Tape Nos. 37-39: General (Box 197, f. 65)
    - Tape Nos. 1-7: Johns Hopkins University (Box 197, f. 66)
    - Tape Nos. 8-15: Johns Hopkins University (Box 197, f. 67)
    - Tape Nos. 16-21: Johns Hopkins University (Box 197, f. 68)
    - Tape Nos. 22-30: Johns Hopkins University (Box 197, f. 69)
    - Tape Nos. 31-43: Johns Hopkins University: Leopold, Hewlett, Lowenheim, du Pont, Introduction (Box 197, f. 70)
    - Tape Nos. 44-46: Johns Hopkins University: Rough draft, Comments Chapter 3, Letters, Revision-Chapter 22 (Box 197, f. 71)
    - Tape Nos. 47-54: Final draft structure of American Industry, Commentary and Criticism, Comments on Frier (Box 197, f. 72)
  - Subseries C. Videos, 1990-1995
    This subseries contains a copy of a video of "American Interests," Part 2, ca. 1990, on which Alfred Chandler was interviewed, and a copy of the 1995 Harvard commencement exercises, at which Chandler received the Distinguished Service Award.
    - American Interest, Part. 2 video, ca. 1990 (Box 246, f. 2)
    - 1995 Harvard Commencement video, 8 June 1995 (Box 246, f. 3)
- Series VII. HBS and HU Administration and Program Records [Restricted], 1959-1998
  This series consists of Harvard Business School and Harvard University administrative records kept by Alfred Chandler and include committee, teaching and program records, as well as records from Harvard Studies in Business History records and the Business History Foundation.
  Harvard Business School and Harvard University administrative records are restricted for 50 years from the date of creation. See Archivist for more information.
  - Subseries A. General Administrative Records, 1970-1998
    This subseries consists of material related to Alfred Chandler’s participation with HBS and Harvard University committees and programs. This subseries includes administrative and committee correspondence, memos, minutes and publications, and material from projects sponsored by HBS and Harvard University.
    This subseries is restricted until 2048. See Archivist for more information.
    Note that folder titles have been redacted.
    - Account #662: 1977-1983 (Box R-1, f. 1)
    - Account #665: 1982 (Box R-1, f. 2)
    - Account #867: 1977-1978 (Box R-1, f. 3)
    - Account #835: 1983 (Box R-1, f. 4)
    - Account #834: 1978-1993 (Box R-1, f. 5)
    - Advanced Management Program: undated (Box R-1, f. 6)
    - Alumni Relations: 1989 (Box R-1, f. 7)
    - Andrews, Kenneth: 1981-1982 (Box R-1, f. 8)
    - Appointments-Standing Committee: 1983 (Box R-1, f. 9)
    - Archives: 1989-1990 (Box R-1, f. 10)
    - Armour, Tim: 1983 (Box R-1, f. 11)
    - Baker Library: 1978-1987 (Box R-1, f. 12)
    - Baker Library: 1978-1987 (Box R-1, f. 13)
    - Baker Library: 1989 (Box R-1, f. 14)
    - Berg, Norman (Box R-1, f. 15)
    - Bok, Derek C.: 1979-1984 (Box R-1, f. 16)
    - Budget: 1980-1981 (Box R-1, f. 17)
    - HSB Bulletin: 1978-1983 (Box R-1, f. 18)
    - Business and Economic Sociology: 1983 (Box R-1, f. 19)
    - Business and Society Discussion Group: Roy Corey: 1972-1984 (Box R-1, f. 20)
    - Business History at HBS (Box R-1, f. 21)
    - Business History Discretionary Account 99-526: 1988 (Box R-1, f. 22)
    - Business History Group: 1981 (Box R-1, f. 23)
    - Business History Review: 1973 (Box R-1, f. 24)
    - Business History Review: 1974-1976 (Box R-2, f. 1)
    - Business History Review: 1976-1979 (Box R-2, f. 2)
    - Business History Review: 1977-1980 (Box R-2, f. 3)
    - Business History Review: 1981-1983 (Box R-2, f. 4)
    - Business History Review: 1981-1984 (Box R-2, f. 5)
    - Business History Review: 1984-1987 (Box R-2, f. 6)
    - Business History Review: 1989-1991 (Box R-2, f. 7)
    - Business History Review: 1991 (Box R-2, f. 8)
    - Business History Review: 1994-1995 (Box R-2, f. 9)
    - Business History Review: 1998 (Box R-2, f. 10)
    - Business History Review: Advisory Board: undated (Box R-2, f. 11)
    - Business History Review: Burk, Thomas, R.: 1987-1989 (Box R-2, f. 12)
    - Business History Review: Genovese, Eugene /Albro, Martin: 1977 (Box R-2, f. 13)
    - Business History Review: Payments/Permissions: undated (Box R-2, f. 14)
    - Business History Review: Search for Editor (Howard Dichman): undated (Box R-2, f. 15)
    - Business Policy Area Committee: 1972-1973 (Box R-2, f. 16)
    - Carpenter, Ken: Kress Room: 1972-1982 (Box R-2, f. 17)
    - Center for European Studies: 1985 (Box R-2, f. 18)
    - Center for International Affairs: 1972-1973 (Box R-2, f. 19)
    - Chandler: Faculty Plans: 1988 (Box R-2, f. 20)
    - Chandler: Outside Activities: 1989 (Box R-2, f. 21)
    - Chandler: Travel Grant: 1990-1994 (Box R-2, f. 22)
    - Chatfield, Mary: Baker Library: 1979-1982 (Box R-2, f. 23)
    - Core Course: 1977-1980 (Box R-2, f. 24)
    - Core Curriculum: 1980-1984 (Box R-2, f. 25)
    - Core Program: Subcommittee on History/Rosovsky: 1978-1984 (Box R-2, f. 26-28)
    - Corey Committee: Concepts of the Corporation: 1984 (Box R-3, f. 1-5)
    - Corey, Raymond: Div. of Research: 1970-1987 (Box R-3, f. 6)
    - Course Development: 1973 (Box R-3, f. 7)
    - DBA Requirements: 1979 (Box R-3, f. 8)
    - Division of Research: Accounts: 1982 (Box R-3, f. 9)
    - Division of Research: Progress Reports/Other: 1972-1979 (Box R-3, f. 10)
    - Division of Research: Research Progress Reports: 1973-1976 (Box R-3, f. 11)
    - Division of Research: Research Progress: 1978-1984 (Box R-3, f. 12)
    - Division of Research: 1982 (Box R-3, f. 13)
    - Doctoral Abstracts: 1971-1992 (Box R-3, f. 14)
    - Doctoral Environment Committee: 1971-1972 (Box R-3, f. 15-16)
    - Doctoral Program: "Special Field in Business Policy": undated (Box R-3, f. 17)
    - Doctoral Program: "Special Fields Proposals": 1972-1973 (Box R-4, f. 1-3)
    - Donald: Dr. Aida: HUP: 1976 (Box R-4, f. 4)
    - Economics Experiment: Harvard: 1982-1985 (Box R-4, f. 5)
    - Educational Review Committee: 1972-1975 (Box R-4, f. 6-8)
    - Educational Review Committee: 1973-1974 (Box R-4, f. 9-10)
    - Educational Review Committee: 1974-1975 (Box R-4, f. 11)
    - Eliot House: 1973-1989 (Box R-4, f. 12)
    - Ethics and the Professions, Program in: Kennedy School: 1986-1988 (Box R-4, f. 13)
    - Ethics and the Professions: Thompson, Dennis: 1987-1988 (Box R-4, f. 14)
    - Environmental Analysis and Corporate Planning Committee: 1972-1973 (Box R-4, f. 15)
    - Faculty HBS: General Memos: 1970-1971 (Box R-5, f. 1-2)
    - Faculty Meetings/Minutes: 1976-1984 (Box R-5, f. 3)
    - Faculty Memoranda: 1972-1973 (Box R-5, f. 4)
    - Fouraker, Lawrence E., Dean: 1971-1978 (Box R-5, f. 5)
    - General Management Area: 1985 (Box R-5, f. 6)
    - General Management Area: undated (Box R-5, f. 7-8)
    - General Management Area: Uyterhoeven: undated (Box R-5, f. 9)
    - Gras/N.S.B. Fellowship: 1980-1988 (Box R-5, f. 10)
    - Great Northern History: HSB Press: 1985-1987 (Box R-5, f. 11)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: 1986-1987 (Box R-5, f. 12)
    - Harvard-JH University Correspondence: In re-job contract, etc.: 1970-1971 (Box R-5, f. 13)
    - Harvard Business Review: 1970-1971 (Box R-5, f. 14)
    - Harvard Business Review: 1972-1987 (Box R-5, f. 15-16)
    - Harvard Business Review: 1990 (Box R-5, f. 17)
    - Harvard Business School: Admissions: 1983 (Box R-5, f. 18)
    - Harvard Business School: Committees and Members: 1979 (Box R-5, f. 19)
    - Harvard Business School: HBS Fund: 1976-1978 (Box R-5, f. 20)
    - Harvard Business School: General matters, Memoranda, Secretarial contracts: 1970-1971 (Box R-5, f. 21)
    - Harvard Business School: Grades: 1989 (Box R-5, f. 22)
    - Harvard Business School: MBA Program: 1979 (Box R-5, f. 23)
    - Harvard Business School: Personal: 1971-1973 (Box R-5, f. 24)
    - Harvard Business School Press: 1984-1988 (Box R-5, f. 25)
    - Harvard Business School Press: Hofsommer, Don, L.: 1994-1996 (Box R-5, f. 26)
    - Harvard College Fund: undated (Box R-5, f. 27)
    - Harvard Entrepreneurs: Harvard College: 1981-1982 (Box R-5, f. 28)
    - Harvard Library Bulletin: 1981-1982 (Box R-5, f. 29)
    - Harvard University: Core Curriculum: 1979 (Box R-6, f. 1)
    - Harvard University: Miscellaneous: 1975-1980 (Box R-6, f. 2)
    - Harvard University Press: 1971-1973 (Box R-6, f. 3)
    - Harvard University Press: 1973-1987 (Box R-6, f. 4-6)
    - Harvard University Press: 1979-1986 (Box R-6, f. 7)
    - Harvard University Press: Bilby Mss.: 1980-1983 (Box R-6, f. 8)
    - Harvard University Press: Blondheim Mss.: 1991-1990 (Box R-6, f. 9)
    - Harvard University Press: Future Policy Committee: 1981-1982 (Box R-6, f. 10)
    - Hayes, Samuel L., III: 1987-1982 (Box R-6, f. 11)
    - Hidy, Ralph and Muriel: 1971-1985 (Box R-6, f. 12)
    - Higher Degrees in the History of American Civilization-Committee: 1973-1989 (Box R-6, f. 13-14)
    - History/History and Literature: 18th Century British History-Ad Hoc Committee: 1980 (Box R-6, f. 15)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee: 1975-1976 (Box R-6, f. 16)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee: 1976 (Box R-6, f. 17)
    - Individual Students Program: undated (Box R-6, f. 18)
    - Individual Studies Program: undated (Box R-6, f. 19)
    - Industrial Policy Colloquium: undated (Box R-6, f. 20)
    - Information Resources Policy Committee: undated (Box R-6, f. 21)
    - International Ad Hoc Committee: 1982-1983 (Box R-6, f. 22-23)
    - International Strategy Study Group: 1982 (Box R-6, f. 24)
    - Kipp, Lawrence (Baker Librarian): 1973-1995 (Box R-6, f. 25)
    - Library (Lovett): 1971-1972 (Box R-7, f. 1)
    - Library Policy Committee: 1971-1972 (Box R-7, f. 2)
    - Library Policy Committee: 1972-1973 (Box R-7, f. 3)
    - Lombard, Dean: 1971-1980 (Box R-7, f. 4)
    - Lovett, Robert: Archives: 1972-1978 (Box R-7, f. 5)
    - McArthur, John H., Dean: 1987-1984 (Box R-7, f. 6)
    - McCraw, Thomas: 1979-1986 (Box R-7, f. 7-8)
    - Martin, Albro: Business History Review: undated (Box R-7, f. 9)
    - MBA Faculty Memoranda: 1972-1974 (Box R-7, f. 10)
    - May, Kathryn Neeld: 1978-1987 (Box R-7, f. 11)
    - Porter, Michael: 1982-1983; Outside Activities of Faculty: 1978-1987 (Box R-7, f. 12)
    - Research Plans: 1977-1978 (Box R-7, f. 13)
    - Research Policy committee: 1988-1989 (Box R-7, f. 14)
    - Rosenbloom, Pro Richard: 1971-1983 (Box R-7, f. 15)
    - Rudenstine, Neil: 1995 (Box R-7, f. 16)
    - Salmon, Walter J.: 1975-1977 (Box R-7, f. 17)
    - Second Year Subcommittee (notice of course name change): 1973 (Box R-7, f. 18)
    - Skouras Papers: Archives: 1982-1997 (Box R-7, f. 19)
    - Sloan Grant to HU: 1973-1981 (Box R-7, f. 20)
    - Social, Economic and Political Environment of Business-Subcommittee: 1973 (Box R-7, f. 21)
    - Strategic Issues Study Group: 1982 (Box R-7, f. 22)
    - Straus (Isidor) Professorship: 1975-1982 (Box R-7, f. 23)
    - Time Horizons on American Management (HBS Joint Project): 1990 (Box R-7, f. 24)
    - Time Horizons, p. 1-26, 2nd draft, 1990 (Box R-28, f. 1-2)
    - Time Horizons, 1990 (Box R-28, f. 3)
    - Time Horizons, 1992 (Box R-28, f. 4)
    - Uyterhoeven, Hugo: 1981 (Box R-7, f. 25)
    - Vernon, Raymond: 1977 (Box R-7, f. 26)
    - Vietor, Richard H.K.: 1981-1987 (Box R-7, f. 27)
    - Visiting Committee (HBS): 1971 (Box R-7, f. 28)
    - Visiting Scholar Program: Mokhtari, Fariborz, L.: 1988 (Box R-7, f. 29)
  - Subseries B. Harvard Studies in Business History, 1959-1990
    This subseries consists of records of the Harvard Studies in Business History series that were inherited in 1971 by Alfred Chandler from Ralph Hidy (who inherited some of these records from Henrietta Larson). These records were presented to Alfred Chandler when he became editor of the series. They consist of general business, copyrights, and other topics related to the management of this project.
    General files have been placed first, arranged chronologically, and the rest have been arranged chronologically based on earliest date of subject
    This subseries is restricted until 2040. See Archivist for more information
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General (Contracts, Royalties): 1931-1949 (Box R-8, f. 1)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1959 (Box R-8, f. 2)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1960-1962 (Box R-8, f. 3)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1963 (Box R-8, f. 4)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1967 (Box R-8, f. 5)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1968-1971 (Box R-8, f. 6)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1969-1971 (Box R-8, f. 7)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: General: 1971-1984 (Box R-8, f. 8)
    - Florentine Merchants in the Age of the Medici by G.R.R. Richards: 1928-1932 (Box R-8, f. 9)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Isaac Hicks by Robert Davison: 1953- 1960 (Box R-8, f. 10)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Isaac Hicks by Robert Davison: 1957- 1959 (Box R-8, f. 11)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Isaac Hicks by Robert Davison: 1960- 1962 (Box R-8, f. 12)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Isaac Hicks by Robert Davison: 1963- 1969 (Box R-8, f. 13)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Charles Ilfeld Company, by William J. Parish: 1957-1961 (Box R-8, f. 14)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: C.J. Kennedy and Virkler Legate: 1959- 1960 (Box R-8, f. 15)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Revolving Fund: 1961-1962 (Box R-8, f. 16)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Medici by deRoover: 1962-1970 (Box R-8, f. 17)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Arthur Cole: 1970-1974 (Box R-8, f. 18)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Robert Davies: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 19)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Freundengerger: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 20)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: G. Garlund: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 21)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Daniel Horowitz: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 22)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Lightner: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 23)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: D. Nelson: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 24)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Villard: 1972-1973 (Box R-8, f. 25)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Robertson-Pollard Manuscript: 1975-1976 (Box R-8, f. 26)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Morikawa, Prof. Hidemasa: 1977-1980 (Box R-8, f. 27)
    - Harvard Studies in Business History: Gordon Boyce: 1990 (Box R-8, f. 28)
  - Subseries C. Administration and Program Records Removed from Teaching Records, 1971-1998
    This subseries consist of minutes, memos, and correspondence related to the administrative functions of the Business History courses and seminars at Harvard Business School.
    This subseries is restricted until 2048. See Archivist for more information